[{"Response":"Very satisfied","Percentage of respondents":22.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly satisfied","Percentage of respondents":49.3,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither satisfied nor dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":12.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":9.6,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":5.9,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with your local area as a place to live?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very satisfied","Percentage of respondents":8.8,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly satisfied","Percentage of respondents":40.2,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither satisfied nor dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":19.0,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Fairly dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":18.7,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Very dissatisfied","Percentage of respondents":13.2,"Question":"Overall, how satisfied or dissatisfied are you with the way Lambeth Council runs things?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Strongly agree","Percentage of respondents":7.3,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Slightly agree","Percentage of respondents":25.6,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Neither agree nor disagree","Percentage of respondents":26.5,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Slightly disagree","Percentage of respondents":22.7,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Strongly disagree","Percentage of respondents":17.9,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that Lambeth Council provides value for money?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Keeps us very well informed","Percentage of respondents":8.3,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Keeps us fairly well informed","Percentage of respondents":39.9,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Gives us only a limited amount of information","Percentage of respondents":27.2,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Doesn't tell us much at all about what it does","Percentage of respondents":24.5,"Question":"How well do you think Lambeth Council keeps residents informed about the services and benefits it provides?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Definitely agree","Percentage of respondents":4.2,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Tend to agree","Percentage of respondents":23.8,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Tend to disagree","Percentage of respondents":34.7,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022},{"Response":"Definitely disagree","Percentage of respondents":37.3,"Question":"To what extent do you agree or disagree that you can influence decisions affecting your local area?","Year":2022}]